Hurry up and choose.
Wait.
I'll give it to you.
He Shi,
I can't believe
you could be so cruel.
Li Zhangxin,
I'm warning you.
From now on in the He family,
you'd better behave.
If you dare to frame me and He Shi again,
I have plenty of ways to kill you.
It's my fault.
I didn't guard against He Shi.
Second Brother,
where there's life, there's hope.
They can run for now,
but they can't hide forever.
I never thought
He Shi would use me against you.
True.
From the moment he crashed into me,
family
meant nothing to him.
I won't let this tragedy happen again.
Yu,
I've found a good match for you.
She is Liang Chunsheng,
the heiress of the Liang Group.
She's been studying abroad
and just came back recently.
Go meet her this afternoon.
I have no intention
of getting married right now.
This is an order,
not a discussion.
Marrying Ms. Liang
will only benefit the He family.
She is a real beauty.
What are we doing today?
I'm going on a blind date.
You're still going to see other men?
Then
what are we?
A one-night stand.
You're just like these things.
Boring once tried.
Shut up.
Turn around.
Walk out.
Get lost.
I'm sorry.
I was delayed by some personal matters.
You look more handsome
than in your photos.
Sorry, Ms. Liang.
Actually, this blind date
wasn't really my idea.
And you don't look
like you're short of men, either.
So
why don't we just go back
and tell our parents it didn't work out,
okay?
But I'm
very satisfied with you.
You must be joking, Ms. Liang.
I'm serious.
A guy like you with good looks,
family background,
and character
must have a lot of girls
chasing after you.
One more won't hurt.
I wouldn't mind.
I'm sorry, Ms. Liang.
I already have someone I like.
So you're not together yet.
I have no interest
in other women.
There's no man I, Liang Chunsheng, want
but can't get.
Where did all this come from?
Hello, Mrs. He.
I'm Liang Chunsheng.
I brought you some gifts
for our first meeting.
You're too kind, Ms. Liang.
It's my pleasure.
Take these upstairs,
and ask the second young master
to come down.
Yes. Go quickly.
Come,
please have a seat, Ms. Liang.
That nanny I just saw
is quite pretty.
She's He Shi's wife,
Shu Roujing.
The eldest daughter-in-law.
What kind of pearls are these?
They look better than mine.
Really?
Liang Chunsheng,
what are you doing here?
Aren't you happy to see your fiancée?
Nothing is settled yet.
Where are you going?
To find Xiaomei.
I heard
Mr. He recently found
his long-lost daughter.
It's this Xiaomei, right?
Yes.
Let me tell you,
you have no idea
how manipulative this woman is.
She actually disguised herself as a nanny
to sneak into the He family.
This one is pretty good.
Really?
Give it a try.
What are you whispering about?
You'll find out when the time comes.
Zhangxin,
if you need any help,
just ask.
I hope
I can be someone you trust.
It's nothing that serious.
I just saw Miss Liang arrive.
She's quite pretty.
Aren't you going to keep her company?
I already rejected her.
I didn't expect her to show up here.
She's got her eye on you.
That's none of my business.
Anyway,
there's no way I'm marrying her.
Why?
She's so pretty,
and she studied abroad.
Zhangxin,
in my eyes,
you are the best.
You're quite biased
as a brother.
I hope one day,
we can be
more than just siblings.
Sister-in-law,
It's not too late to call you
my sister-in-law now,
is it?
Ms. Liang,
You don't mind if I borrow
your brother for a date,
do you?
Then you should ask my brother,
not me.
You're quite a reasonable sister.
I've heard Liang Chunsheng came today.
What a pity
I didn't run into him.
I'm talking to you.
Hurry up and help me change.
You're a grown man.
Can't you change your own clothes?
Interesting.
The sun must have risen in the west today.
You...
Ouch!
He Shi!
I'm no longer the Shu Roujing
who lets people bully her.
When did you...
Haven't you noticed I've been
leaving early
and coming home late recently?
This coach just won
the Lumpinee gold belt.
All right,
take a break.
Good practice.
Zhangxin inspired me.
I can't be soft-hearted
with people like you.
Starting today,
we sleep in separate rooms.
You sleep in the guest room.
How dare you make demands of me!
Damn!
Just you wait.
You actually let Shu Roujing
walk all over you.
He Shi,
you're really useless.
I'm useless?
I'll show you whether I'm useless or not.
Again?
Aren't you tired?